var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "الْإِبِلِ",
        "answer": "the camels",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 8,
        "tlit": "l-ibili",
        "frequency": 3,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " أَفَلَا يَنْظُرُونَ إِلَى الْإِبِلِ كَيْفَ خُلِقَتْ",
        "rootWord": "أ ب ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "إِبِل",
        "waznEnglish": "camels",
        "waznTlit": "ibil",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَاكَ",
        "answer": "(there) come to you",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "rootWordId": 12,
        "tlit": "atāka",
        "frequency": 549,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " هَلْ أَتَاكَ حَدِيثُ الْغَاشِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "أ ت ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَتَى",
        "waznEnglish": "to come, to bring",
        "waznTlit": "atā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 264,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "456",
        "rootWordId": 32,
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": 461,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 20,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى الْأَرْضِ كَيْفَ سُطِحَتْ",
        "rootWord": "أ ر ض",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أ ر ض",
        "waznEnglish": "the Earth, land",
        "waznTlit": "hamza rā ḍād",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 461,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "655",
        "rootWordId": 58,
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": 663,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " لَيْسَ لَهُمْ طَعَامٌ إِلَّا مِنْ ضَرِيعٍ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "إِلَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "except",
        "waznTlit": "illā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Exceptive particle)",
        "waznFreq": 663,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "But",
        "pcklId": "656",
        "rootWordId": 58,
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": 663,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 23,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " إِلَّا مَنْ تَوَلَّىٰ وَكَفَرَ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "إِلَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "except",
        "waznTlit": "illā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Exceptive particle)",
        "waznFreq": 663,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2833",
        "rootWordId": 61,
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": 2851,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 24,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَيُعَذِّبُهُ اللَّهُ الْعَذَابَ الْأَكْبَرَ",
        "rootWord": "أ ل ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱللَّه",
        "waznEnglish": "Allah",
        "waznTlit": "allah",
        "waznType": "Proper noun",
        "waznFreq": 2699,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "towards",
        "pcklId": "734",
        "rootWordId": 63,
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": 742,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " أَفَلَا يَنْظُرُونَ إِلَى الْإِبِلِ كَيْفَ خُلِقَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَىٰ",
        "rootWordType": "preposition",
        "wazn": "إِلَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to, toward, until",
        "waznTlit": "ilā",
        "waznType": "Preposition",
        "waznFreq": 742,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَى",
        "answer": "And towards",
        "pcklId": "735",
        "rootWordId": 63,
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": 742,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 18,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى السَّمَاءِ كَيْفَ رُفِعَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَىٰ",
        "rootWordType": "preposition",
        "wazn": "إِلَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to, toward, until",
        "waznTlit": "ilā",
        "waznType": "Preposition",
        "waznFreq": 742,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَى",
        "answer": "And towards",
        "pcklId": "736",
        "rootWordId": 63,
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": 742,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 19,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى الْجِبَالِ كَيْفَ نُصِبَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَىٰ",
        "rootWordType": "preposition",
        "wazn": "إِلَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to, toward, until",
        "waznTlit": "ilā",
        "waznType": "Preposition",
        "waznFreq": 742,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَى",
        "answer": "And towards",
        "pcklId": "737",
        "rootWordId": 63,
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": 742,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 20,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى الْأَرْضِ كَيْفَ سُطِحَتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَىٰ",
        "rootWordType": "preposition",
        "wazn": "إِلَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to, toward, until",
        "waznTlit": "ilā",
        "waznType": "Preposition",
        "waznFreq": 742,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to Us",
        "pcklId": "738",
        "rootWordId": 63,
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": 742,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 25,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّ إِلَيْنَا إِيَابَهُمْ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَىٰ",
        "rootWordType": "preposition",
        "wazn": "إِلَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to, toward, until",
        "waznTlit": "ilā",
        "waznType": "Preposition",
        "waznFreq": 742,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "آنِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "boiling",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "rootWordId": 81,
        "tlit": "āniyatin",
        "frequency": 36,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " تُسْقَىٰ مِنْ عَيْنٍ آنِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "أ ن ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ءَانِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "come (the) time",
        "waznTlit": "āniyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيَابَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(will be) their return",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "rootWordId": 83,
        "tlit": "iyābahum",
        "frequency": 17,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 25,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّ إِلَيْنَا إِيَابَهُمْ",
        "rootWord": "أ و ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "إِيَاب",
        "waznEnglish": "Repeat praises",
        "waznTlit": "iyāb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "مَبْثُوثَةٌ",
        "answer": "spread out",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "rootWordId": 96,
        "tlit": "mabthūthatun",
        "frequency": 9,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 16,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَزَرَابِيُّ مَبْثُوثَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ب ث ث",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَبْثُوثَة",
        "waznEnglish": "and dispersing",
        "waznTlit": "mabthūthat",
        "waznType": "Passive participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِبَالِ",
        "answer": "the mountains",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "rootWordId": 219,
        "tlit": "l-jibāli",
        "frequency": 41,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 19,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى الْجِبَالِ كَيْفَ نُصِبَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ج ب ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جَبَل",
        "waznEnglish": "hill",
        "waznTlit": "jabal",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 39,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "جَارِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "flowing",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "rootWordId": 242,
        "tlit": "jāriyatun",
        "frequency": 64,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 12,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فِيهَا عَيْنٌ جَارِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ج ر ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جَارِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "flow",
        "waznTlit": "jāriyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّةٍ",
        "answer": "a garden",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "rootWordId": 267,
        "tlit": "jannatin",
        "frequency": 201,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 10,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فِي جَنَّةٍ عَالِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ج ن ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جَنَّة",
        "waznEnglish": "covered",
        "waznTlit": "jannat",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 147,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "جُوعٍ",
        "answer": "hunger",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 278,
        "tlit": "jūʿin",
        "frequency": 5,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " لَا يُسْمِنُ وَلَا يُغْنِي مِنْ جُوعٍ",
        "rootWord": "ج و ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جُوع",
        "waznEnglish": "you will be hungry",
        "waznTlit": "jūʿ",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 4,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "حَدِيثُ",
        "answer": "(the) news",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "rootWordId": 297,
        "tlit": "ḥadīthu",
        "frequency": 36,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " هَلْ أَتَاكَ حَدِيثُ الْغَاشِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ح د ث",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَدِيث",
        "waznEnglish": "Do you tell them",
        "waznTlit": "ḥadīth",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 28,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) their account",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "rootWordId": 316,
        "tlit": "ḥisābahum",
        "frequency": 109,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 26,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ إِنَّ عَلَيْنَا حِسَابَهُمْ",
        "rootWord": "ح س ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حِسَاب",
        "waznEnglish": "(do) you think",
        "waznTlit": "ḥisāb",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun (form III) (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 39,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "حَامِيَةً",
        "answer": "intensely hot",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 356,
        "tlit": "ḥāmiyatan",
        "frequency": 6,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " تَصْلَىٰ نَارًا حَامِيَةً",
        "rootWord": "ح م ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَامِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "it will be heated [on it]",
        "waznTlit": "ḥāmiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاشِعَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) humbled",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "rootWordId": 409,
        "tlit": "khāshiʿatun",
        "frequency": 17,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وُجُوهٌ يَوْمَئِذٍ خَاشِعَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "خ ش ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَاشِع",
        "waznEnglish": "And (will be) humbled",
        "waznTlit": "khāshiʿ",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 14,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "خُلِقَتْ",
        "answer": "they are created",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "rootWordId": 431,
        "tlit": "khuliqat",
        "frequency": 261,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " أَفَلَا يَنْظُرُونَ إِلَى الْإِبِلِ كَيْفَ خُلِقَتْ",
        "rootWord": "خ ل ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَلَقَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to create",
        "waznTlit": "khalaqa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 184,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَذَكِّرْ",
        "answer": "So remind",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "rootWordId": 511,
        "tlit": "fadhakkir",
        "frequency": 292,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 21,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَذَكِّرْ إِنَّمَا أَنْتَ مُذَكِّرٌ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ك ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ذُكِّرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to remind",
        "waznTlit": "dhukkira",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 18,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "مُذَكِّرٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a reminder",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "rootWordId": 511,
        "tlit": "mudhakkirun",
        "frequency": 292,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 21,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَذَكِّرْ إِنَّمَا أَنْتَ مُذَكِّرٌ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ك ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مُذَكِّر",
        "waznEnglish": "Remember",
        "waznTlit": "mudhakkir",
        "waznType": "Active participle (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَاضِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "satisfied",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "rootWordId": 561,
        "tlit": "rāḍiyatun",
        "frequency": 73,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 9,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " لِسَعْيِهَا رَاضِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ر ض و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَاضِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "will be pleased",
        "waznTlit": "rāḍiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 4,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رُفِعَتْ",
        "answer": "it is raised",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "rootWordId": 573,
        "tlit": "rufiʿat",
        "frequency": 29,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 18,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى السَّمَاءِ كَيْفَ رُفِعَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ر ف ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَفَعَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to raise",
        "waznTlit": "rafaʿa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 22,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْفُوعَةٌ",
        "answer": "raised high",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "rootWordId": 573,
        "tlit": "marfūʿatun",
        "frequency": 29,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فِيهَا سُرُرٌ مَرْفُوعَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ر ف ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَّرْفُوعَة",
        "waznEnglish": "and We raised",
        "waznTlit": "marfūʿat",
        "waznType": "Passive participle (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "سُرُرٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) thrones",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "rootWordId": 681,
        "tlit": "sururun",
        "frequency": 44,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فِيهَا سُرُرٌ مَرْفُوعَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "س ر ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سُرُر",
        "waznEnglish": "pleasing",
        "waznTlit": "surur",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 6,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "سُطِحَتْ",
        "answer": "it is spread out",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 687,
        "tlit": "suṭiḥat",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 20,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى الْأَرْضِ كَيْفَ سُطِحَتْ",
        "rootWord": "س ط ح",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "س ط ح",
        "waznEnglish": "to spread out",
        "waznTlit": "sīn ṭā ḥā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمُصَيْطِرٍ",
        "answer": "a controller",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "rootWordId": 688,
        "tlit": "bimuṣayṭirin",
        "frequency": 16,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 22,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " لَسْتَ عَلَيْهِمْ بِمُصَيْطِرٍ",
        "rootWord": "س ط ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مُصَيْطِر",
        "waznEnglish": "they write",
        "waznTlit": "muṣayṭir",
        "waznType": "Active participle (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لِسَعْيِهَا",
        "answer": "With their effort",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "rootWordId": 692,
        "tlit": "lisaʿyihā",
        "frequency": 30,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 9,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " لِسَعْيِهَا رَاضِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "س ع ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَعْي",
        "waznEnglish": "and strives",
        "waznTlit": "saʿī",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 10,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تُسْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "They will be given to drink",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "rootWordId": 704,
        "tlit": "tus'qā",
        "frequency": 25,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " تُسْقَىٰ مِنْ عَيْنٍ آنِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "س ق ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَقَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to water, to give drink",
        "waznTlit": "saqā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 12,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْمَعُ",
        "answer": "they will hear",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "rootWordId": 722,
        "tlit": "tasmaʿu",
        "frequency": 185,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 11,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " لَا تَسْمَعُ فِيهَا لَاغِيَةً",
        "rootWord": "س م ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَمِعَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to hear, to listen",
        "waznTlit": "samiʿa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 78,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسْمِنُ",
        "answer": "it nourishes",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 725,
        "tlit": "yus'minu",
        "frequency": 4,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " لَا يُسْمِنُ وَلَا يُغْنِي مِنْ جُوعٍ",
        "rootWord": "س م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يُسْمِنُ",
        "waznEnglish": "to nourish",
        "waznTlit": "yus'minu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "rootWordId": 726,
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": 381,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 18,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى السَّمَاءِ كَيْفَ رُفِعَتْ",
        "rootWord": "س م و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَمَآء",
        "waznEnglish": "[I] (have) named her",
        "waznTlit": "samā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 310,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "مَصْفُوفَةٌ",
        "answer": "lined up",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "rootWordId": 849,
        "tlit": "maṣfūfatun",
        "frequency": 14,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 15,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَنَمَارِقُ مَصْفُوفَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ص ف ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَصْفُوفَة",
        "waznEnglish": "(when) lined up",
        "waznTlit": "maṣfūfat",
        "waznType": "Passive participle (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَصْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "They will burn",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "rootWordId": 858,
        "tlit": "taṣlā",
        "frequency": 25,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " تَصْلَىٰ نَارًا حَامِيَةً",
        "rootWord": "ص ل ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَصْلَى",
        "waznEnglish": "to burn",
        "waznTlit": "yaṣlā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 13,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرِيعٍ",
        "answer": "a bitter thorny plant",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 886,
        "tlit": "ḍarīʿin",
        "frequency": 8,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " لَيْسَ لَهُمْ طَعَامٌ إِلَّا مِنْ ضَرِيعٍ",
        "rootWord": "ض ر ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ضَرِيع",
        "waznEnglish": "they humbled themselves",
        "waznTlit": "ḍarīʿ",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامٌ",
        "answer": "food",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "rootWordId": 911,
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmun",
        "frequency": 48,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " لَيْسَ لَهُمْ طَعَامٌ إِلَّا مِنْ ضَرِيعٍ",
        "rootWord": "ط ع م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "طَعَام",
        "waznEnglish": "taste it",
        "waznTlit": "ṭaʿām",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 24,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُعَذِّبُهُ",
        "answer": "Then will punish him",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "rootWordId": 968,
        "tlit": "fayuʿadhibuhu",
        "frequency": 373,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 24,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَيُعَذِّبُهُ اللَّهُ الْعَذَابَ الْأَكْبَرَ",
        "rootWord": "ع ذ ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَذَّبَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to punish",
        "waznTlit": "ʿadhaba",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 41,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابَ",
        "answer": "(with) the punishment",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "rootWordId": 968,
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": 373,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 24,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَيُعَذِّبُهُ اللَّهُ الْعَذَابَ الْأَكْبَرَ",
        "rootWord": "ع ذ ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَذَاب",
        "waznEnglish": "and He will punish",
        "waznTlit": "ʿadhāb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 322,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عَالِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "elevated",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "rootWordId": 1018,
        "tlit": "ʿāliyatin",
        "frequency": 70,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 10,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فِي جَنَّةٍ عَالِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَالِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "and Exalted",
        "waznTlit": "ʿāliyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عَامِلَةٌ",
        "answer": "Laboring",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "rootWordId": 1022,
        "tlit": "ʿāmilatun",
        "frequency": 360,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " عَامِلَةٌ نَاصِبَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ع م ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَامِلَة",
        "waznEnglish": "and do",
        "waznTlit": "ʿāmilat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْنٍ",
        "answer": "a spring",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "rootWordId": 1046,
        "tlit": "ʿaynin",
        "frequency": 65,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " تُسْقَىٰ مِنْ عَيْنٍ آنِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ع ي ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَيْن",
        "waznEnglish": "(having) beautiful eyes",
        "waznTlit": "ʿayn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 57,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْنٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) a spring",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "rootWordId": 1046,
        "tlit": "ʿaynun",
        "frequency": 65,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 12,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فِيهَا عَيْنٌ جَارِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ع ي ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَيْن",
        "waznEnglish": "(having) beautiful eyes",
        "waznTlit": "ʿayn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 57,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَاشِيَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Overwhelming",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "rootWordId": 1064,
        "tlit": "l-ghāshiyati",
        "frequency": 29,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " هَلْ أَتَاكَ حَدِيثُ الْغَاشِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "غ ش و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "غَٰشِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "overcoming",
        "waznTlit": "ghāshiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يُغْنِي",
        "answer": "it avails",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "rootWordId": 1086,
        "tlit": "yugh'nī",
        "frequency": 73,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " لَا يُسْمِنُ وَلَا يُغْنِي مِنْ جُوعٍ",
        "rootWord": "غ ن ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَغْنَتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to avail, to enrich",
        "waznTlit": "aghnat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 28,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَكْبَرَ",
        "answer": "greatest",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "rootWordId": 1254,
        "tlit": "l-akbara",
        "frequency": 161,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 24,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَيُعَذِّبُهُ اللَّهُ الْعَذَابَ الْأَكْبَرَ",
        "rootWord": "ك ب ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَكْبَر",
        "waznEnglish": "they will grow up",
        "waznTlit": "akbar",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 24,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَفَرَ",
        "answer": "and disbelieves",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "rootWordId": 1280,
        "tlit": "wakafara",
        "frequency": 525,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 23,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " إِلَّا مَنْ تَوَلَّىٰ وَكَفَرَ",
        "rootWord": "ك ف ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَفَرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to disbelieve",
        "waznTlit": "kafara",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 289,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَكْوَابٌ",
        "answer": "And cups",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 1301,
        "tlit": "wa-akwābun",
        "frequency": 4,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَكْوَابٌ مَوْضُوعَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ك و ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ك و ب",
        "waznEnglish": "and cups",
        "waznTlit": "kāf wāw bā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 4,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "rootWordId": 1308,
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": 83,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " أَفَلَا يَنْظُرُونَ إِلَى الْإِبِلِ كَيْفَ خُلِقَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ك ي ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ك ي ف",
        "waznEnglish": "How",
        "waznTlit": "kāf yā fā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Interogative particle)",
        "waznFreq": 83,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "rootWordId": 1308,
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": 83,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 18,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى السَّمَاءِ كَيْفَ رُفِعَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ك ي ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ك ي ف",
        "waznEnglish": "How",
        "waznTlit": "kāf yā fā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Interogative particle)",
        "waznFreq": 83,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "rootWordId": 1308,
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": 83,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 19,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى الْجِبَالِ كَيْفَ نُصِبَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ك ي ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ك ي ف",
        "waznEnglish": "How",
        "waznTlit": "kāf yā fā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Interogative particle)",
        "waznFreq": 83,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "rootWordId": 1308,
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": 83,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 20,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى الْأَرْضِ كَيْفَ سُطِحَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ك ي ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ك ي ف",
        "waznEnglish": "How",
        "waznTlit": "kāf yā fā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Interogative particle)",
        "waznFreq": 83,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَاغِيَةً",
        "answer": "vain talk",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "rootWordId": 1336,
        "tlit": "lāghiyatan",
        "frequency": 11,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 11,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " لَا تَسْمَعُ فِيهَا لَاغِيَةً",
        "rootWord": "ل غ و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "لَٰغِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "and make noise",
        "waznTlit": "lāghiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Not is",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "rootWordId": 1363,
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": 89,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " لَيْسَ لَهُمْ طَعَامٌ إِلَّا مِنْ ضَرِيعٍ",
        "rootWord": "ل ي س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ل ي س",
        "waznEnglish": "to not be",
        "waznTlit": "lām yā sīn",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 89,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَسْتَ",
        "answer": "You are not",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "rootWordId": 1363,
        "tlit": "lasta",
        "frequency": 89,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 22,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " لَسْتَ عَلَيْهِمْ بِمُصَيْطِرٍ",
        "rootWord": "ل ي س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ل ي س",
        "waznEnglish": "to not be",
        "waznTlit": "lām yā sīn",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 89,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "نُصِبَتْ",
        "answer": "they are fixed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1474,
        "tlit": "nuṣibat",
        "frequency": 32,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 19,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِلَى الْجِبَالِ كَيْفَ نُصِبَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ن ص ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نُصِبَتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to be fixed, to labour",
        "waznTlit": "nuṣibat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاصِبَةٌ",
        "answer": "exhausted",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "rootWordId": 1474,
        "tlit": "nāṣibatun",
        "frequency": 32,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " عَامِلَةٌ نَاصِبَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ن ص ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَّاصِبَة",
        "waznEnglish": "they are fixed",
        "waznTlit": "nāṣibat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they look",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "rootWordId": 1487,
        "tlit": "yanẓurūna",
        "frequency": 129,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " أَفَلَا يَنْظُرُونَ إِلَى الْإِبِلِ كَيْفَ خُلِقَتْ",
        "rootWord": "ن ظ ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَّظَرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to look, to see",
        "waznTlit": "naẓara",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 87,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاعِمَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) joyful",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "rootWordId": 1492,
        "tlit": "nāʿimatun",
        "frequency": 140,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وُجُوهٌ يَوْمَئِذٍ نَاعِمَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ن ع م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَّاعِمَة",
        "waznEnglish": "then good",
        "waznTlit": "nāʿimat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارًا",
        "answer": "(in) a Fire",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "rootWordId": 1529,
        "tlit": "nāran",
        "frequency": 194,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " تَصْلَىٰ نَارًا حَامِيَةً",
        "rootWord": "ن و ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَار",
        "waznEnglish": "a fire",
        "waznTlit": "nār",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 145,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهٌ",
        "answer": "Faces",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "rootWordId": 1592,
        "tlit": "wujūhun",
        "frequency": 78,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وُجُوهٌ يَوْمَئِذٍ خَاشِعَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "و ج ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "وَجْه",
        "waznEnglish": "[I] have turned",
        "waznTlit": "wajh",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 72,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهٌ",
        "answer": "Faces",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "rootWordId": 1592,
        "tlit": "wujūhun",
        "frequency": 78,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وُجُوهٌ يَوْمَئِذٍ نَاعِمَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "و ج ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "وَجْه",
        "waznEnglish": "[I] have turned",
        "waznTlit": "wajh",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 72,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْضُوعَةٌ",
        "answer": "put in place",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "rootWordId": 1621,
        "tlit": "mawḍūʿatun",
        "frequency": 26,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَكْوَابٌ مَوْضُوعَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "و ض ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَّوْضُوعَة",
        "waznEnglish": "she delivered her",
        "waznTlit": "mawḍūʿat",
        "waznType": "Passive participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "turns away",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "rootWordId": 1648,
        "tlit": "tawallā",
        "frequency": 232,
        "surahnum": 88,
        "ayahnum": 23,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " إِلَّا مَنْ تَوَلَّىٰ وَكَفَرَ",
        "rootWord": "و ل ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَوَلَّىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to turn",
        "waznTlit": "tawallā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form V)",
        "waznFreq": 78,
        "hasRootWord": true
    }
]; 
export default words;